

# 073 9488 278 askarians@me.com

https:// www.linkedin.com/in/ saeed-askariana1288a6b/

Stallgatan 1B, 19432, Stockholm

# Saeed Askarian

#### **About me**

I am a diligent and inquisitive individual, with a passion for programming and a drive to uncover optimal solutions in complex situations. Over the past five years, I have gained experience working in various areas of computer hardware and software. I previously owned and operated a computer store where I expertly assembled and sold computers. I have also worked as an ISP service provider and spent several years as a web designer. However, I subsequently changed my career path, undertaking studies and practical work as a social worker focused on helping children, individuals with mental health disorders, and other target groups. After 15 years, I have decided to re-enter the technology industry and update my knowledge. I am eager to secure a challenging internship that can help me build the skills I need to thrive in large-scale companies.

## **Skills:**

Javascript, HTML, CSS, React. PHP, Node Js., MongoDB. Batch Script, Microsoft Access. Social law.

## **Experience**

2021-2022, Health care counselor, Akademiska hospital Affective ward, outpatient care, Uppsala 2019-2021, Socionom, Uppsala municipality, Children dep. 2003-2011, Self-employed, Study focus Co. Malaysia 1999-2003, Web designer, ISP service

### **Education**

2022-2024, Full stack, E-commerce in Medieinstitutet 2018-2019, Socionom examen (supplementary education) Södertörn 2014-2018, Master of science in social work, USWR, Tehran 2009-2014, Bachelor of science in social work, USWR, Tehran

# Language proficiency

Persian, fluent Swedish, advanced English, advanced

#### **Other**

Silver medal in a national Olympiad of Iranian students of medical sciences 2014, in the field of national health management.